Finding Aid of the UW-Milwaukee Institute of Visual Art Records, 1962-2016
University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee Libraries, Archives Department
- Records, 1962-2003
  - 1. Exhibitions, 1964-2001
    - Waswagoning: People of the Torch, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 4-7)
    - Folk Art Carvings of Northern New Mexico, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 8-11)
    - Master's Exhibition, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 12-13)
    - Connoisseurship: A Question of Quality, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Art Show 15, Alumni Exhibition, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 15-16)
    - Captured Shadows: 19th Century Photographs of Rome and the Acropolis of Athens, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Wauswaiming: Objects from the Chippewa Museum and Cultural Center Collection, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - The Next Door Foundation, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 19-20)
    - Piranesi Etchings from the Dayton Art Institute, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 21-22)
    - A Day Without Art: The National AIDS Awareness Day, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Face, Figure and Form: Art and the Human Condition, 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 24-27)
    - The Matter at Hand: Contemporary Drawing Exhibition, 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 28-30)
    - Stone-Hoey Exhibit, 1989-1990 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - 19th Century Photographs of Greece, Rome and Egypt, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Maya/Portraits Traveling Show, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Photographs of Faculty Research, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Annual Student Competition, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Student Shows, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 6-13)
    - Wild Space Dance, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Ritualistic Spaces, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - New Orleans/Day of the Dead, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Contemporary Art Guild, Janet Fishman Collection, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 17-18)
    - Master's Exhibition, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 19-20)
    - David Sharpe Exhibit, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 21-23)
    - Wright, Robert, In Memory of the Cemetaries of New Orleans, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Feline Motif in Pre-Colombian Art, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 25-26)
    - Alumni Show, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Haitian Art Exhibit, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Images of Summer, Andy Warhol in the Gershan Collection, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Rathsack, L. and M. Tingley Exhibit, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - College for Kids, The Neverending Story Art, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Tingley, Mary, Body Structures Exhibition, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Hine, Lewis, The TVA Project, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - The Quentin and Emmy Lou Schenk Collection of Ethiopia, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 34-35)
    - Rathsack Retrospective, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - Master's Exhibition, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Kentucky Folk Art, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 38-40)
    - Studio 90, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 41-42)
    - Expression 3, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - Barrie Lecture, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 44)
    - Local Vision Publication, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 45)
    - Holy Ranger and His Blues Riders Band, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 46)
    - From Marble into Bronze: Transformations in American Sculpture, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 47-49)
    - A Day Without Art: The National AIDS Awareness Day, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 50)
    - Haitian Benefit, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Annual Student Exhibition, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Japanese Prints, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 3-4)
    - Master's Exhibition, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - National Broadside Exhibition, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 6-7)
    - Verging on Emergence, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 8-9)
    - Golub/Spero Exhibit, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 10-11)
    - The Feline Motif in South American Art, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - International Museum Day, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Alumni Summer Art Show, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - College for Kids, Summer, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Summer Show: Balanceobjekt, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Downfall: Degenerate and Outsider Art in Milwaukee, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Rookwood Art Pottery, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Sculptors on Paper, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Fursman, Frederic Frary, A Rediscovered Impressionist, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 20-23)
    - Mid-America Conference, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - UW System: A System of Sculpture, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Kansas State Show, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Christo: The Umbrellas, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Sculptures of the 20th Century Exhibit, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Art in the Age of Mozart, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - In Tune With Tradition Exhibition, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Personal Intensity, Roger Brown, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 31-34)
    - Master's Exhibition, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - College for Kids, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Polish Posters: Selections from the Golden Age, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Mexican Fine Arts Center Museum, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Andriessen, Richard, An American in Munich, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Haas, Richard, Architectural Drawings, Paintings and Models, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 5-6)
    - Present Tense Exhibit, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 7-9)
    - Rookwood Pottery, Springfield Art Museum, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Mende Cloth Exhibit, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Milwaukee County Fellowship, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Verging on Emergence, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Catherwood Lithos (AGS Collection), 1992 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Student Exhibit, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Schlabowske, Dave Exhibit, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Student Competition, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Master's Exhibition, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Vasiljev, Igor, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Born Under Saturn, Bembenek, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 20-22)
    - Museum Day, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Haitian Benefit Sale, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Irish Fest, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Silent Stones, O'Sullivan, Timothy, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Polish Posters, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Faculty Exhibition, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Itatani, Michiko, New Paintings, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Master's Exhibition, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - The Art of the Map, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - John Colt Retrospective, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 2-3)
    - Passed to the Present, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Verging on Emergence, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Annual Student Exhibition, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Stevens, Brooks, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Narratives of Loss, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 8-10)
    - A Caravaggio at the Hands of Children, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Master's Exhibition, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Haitian Art Exhibit, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Alumni Show, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Victorian Pleasures: An Examination of "Taste", 1993 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Permanent Collection and Arts and Crafts Furniture, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - College for Kids, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Irish Summer School, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Familial Relations, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 19-21)
    - Wisconsin Artist Biennial, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Wisconsin Painters and Sculptors, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Humanities Grant Proposal, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Alumni Exhibition, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - American Arts and Crafts, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Gunderman, Karen and Christopher Davis-Benavides, Recent Work, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 27-28)
    - Linares Exhibition, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 29-30)
    - Asmat Art, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Maya Exhibit/Travel, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Fall Thesis, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Kelly, Mary, 1993-1994 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Ethnic Craft in Coastal Wisconsin, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Desire in Time: Time as Intimacy, Grabner and Kranitzky, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 2-5)
    - Carbone, David, Inner Spectacles, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Foundations 94: A Student Exhibition, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - "Where Do We Go From Here", 1994 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Fishman Collection, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 9-12)
    - Scholarship Show, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Berman, Fred, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 14-15)
    - MA Thesis, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Wisconsin Projects Administration (WPA) Craft Project, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Physical Plant: Public Inquiries, Uncommon Solutions, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 18-20)
    - Haitian Exhibit and Sale, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Industrial Strength Degenerate Art, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Brulc, Lillian, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Art from Around the World, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Confronting Cancer through Art, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 25-26)
    - College for Kids, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Image:Text, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Hartlieb, Ingrid, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Robert Burkert Retrospective, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 30-31)
    - Muybridge, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Parness, Charles, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Studio 94, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Home and Away, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Cartoons, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Thesis Exhibit, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Gustin, Dan, 1994-1995 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Art of Carl McKenzie, 1994-1995 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Balsley, Diane, 1994-1995 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Rath, Ruth Groten, 1994-1995 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Storytellers: Expressionist Narrative, 1994-1995 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Humor and High Adventure, 1994-1995 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Killiam, Brad, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Cohan, Charles, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Morrison, Susan, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Arnold, Catherine, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Di Luzio, Raphael, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Graduate Thesis Exhibit, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Inner Spectacle, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - British Satiric Prints, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Student Competition, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Art of Music, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - MFA Thesis Show, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Sommers, Linda, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Sloan, Jeanette, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - BFA Show, Summer, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - College for Kids, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Handweaver's Guild, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Fischer, Anthony, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Latin American Music Festival, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Alumni Art Competition, Loans, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Art for the Next Century, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Student Scholarship Show, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Dorval, Elton: Humor and High Adventures, 1995-1996 (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Jewels of the Forest, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - Faculty Biennial Exhibition, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - Master Thesis, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - Perez-Bravo, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - Rosin, Paul, 1996-1997 (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - Weber, Marnie, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - Havel, Joseph, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - Lowe, Truman, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 42)
    - Taylor, Jocelyn, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 43)
    - O'Sullivan, Timothy, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 44)
    - Beecroft, Vanessa, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 45)
    - Gonzalez-Forestier, Dominique, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 46)
    - Avery, Eric, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 47)
    - Reuss, Trudie, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 48)
    - Barber, Stephanie, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 49)
    - City/County Exhibit, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 50)
    - Thesis: Anxiety Show, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 51)
    - Rosenberg Collection, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 52)
    - Grabner, Michelle, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 53)
    - Steinkamp, Jennifer, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 54)
    - Car Exhibit, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 55)
    - Van Der Heijden, Liselot, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 56)
    - Ortiz-Torres, Ruben, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 57)
    - Lucas, Kristin, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 58)
    - Tesi, Alexandra, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Bournigault, Rebecca, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Hoffman, Leni, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Bronson, Jessica, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Art Deco: Architecture of Milwaukee, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Ward, Nari, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - McQueen, Steve, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Smith, Lester, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - MFA Thesis Show, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Rainey, Dave, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Collier, Anne, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Parreno, Philippe, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Gaiter,Collette, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Quinones, Nester, 1997-1998 (Box 17, Folder 14-15)
    - Strba, Annelies, 1997-1998 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Wilson, Jane and Louise, 1997-1998 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Nara, Yoshitomo, 1997-1998 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Wood, Kelly, 1997-1998 (Box 17, Folder 19-20)
    - Koester, Joachim, 1997-1998 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Huyghe, Pierre, 1997-1999 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Santiago Loss, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Frank, Nicholas, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Dunning, Jeanne, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Tasset, Tony, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 26-27)
    - Sans/Wurm, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Cattelan, Maurizio, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Wurm, Erwin, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Larson, O'Neil, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Ischar, Doug, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Takashima, Yoko, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Ruppersberg, Allen, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Elesby, Sally, 1998-1999 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - von Hausswolf, Annika, 1998-1999 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Iserman, Jim, 1998-1999 (Box 18, Folder 3-9)
    - Vilmouth, Jean Luc, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Yoshitomo Nara Claim, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Spero, Nancy, Grant for the 7th International Cairo Biennial, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Parr, Martin: Common Sense Exhibit, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Erre Exhibition, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Lambri, Lisa, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Mateus, Christina Exhibition, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Blau, Dick and Jane Gallop, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Villesen, Gitte, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Calderon, Miguel, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Jermolaewa, Anna, Correspondence, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Leiderstam, Matt, 1999-2000 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Lewis, Mark, 1999-2000 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Searle, Bernadette, 1999-2000 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Tzaig, Uri, 1999-2000 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Ghada Amer Exhibit, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 25-26)
    - Pernice, Manfred, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Bertucci, Liwa, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Nilson, Lars, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Stonehouse, Fred, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Beelden, 2000-2001
    - Fischer, Naomi, Exhibit, 2000-2001 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Robbins, David, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Murikami, Takashi, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Hadjithomas, Joanna and Khalil Joreuge, Correspondence, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Niskanen, Pekka, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Tayou, Pascale Marthine, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - Gaba, Meschac, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - Bonde, Peter, Exhibit, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - Kusolwong, Surasi, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - Sooja, Kim, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - Ang, Tiong, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - Claerbout, David, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - 2. Administrative Files, 1962-2003
    The series includes the operational files of the UWM Art Museum. These documents include insurance claims, accession files, loan requests, committee minutes, planning reports, news releases, schedules, calendars, and miscellaneous correspondence. Folders also detail the donations and gifts of art, materials and money to the UWM Art Museum over the years.
    Also included in this series is information regarding two ongoing exhibition series, Fiber R/Evolution and the Women's Autobiographical Artists' Books (WAAB). These exhibitions took place over multiple years, included juried sections, and were often curated in collaboration with other institutions. The Fiber R/Evolution files include correspondence with over 50 artists and an extensive and detailed jury process. The WAAB files include correspondence with 75 women artists and numerous photographs and slides.
    The series is arranged alphabetically by folder heading. These records describe different aspects of managing the Art Museum and include numerous case files and donor correspondence, organized in a last name, first name format.
    Two ongoing exhibitions, Fiber R/Evolution and the Women’s Autobiographical Artists’ Books (WAAB), are split into two subgroups, administrative and artist correspondence, and arranged alphabetically.
    - Abdessmed, Adel, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Ackerman Foundation, Martin S., 1977-1981 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Ackerman/IRS Inquiry, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Anderson, Kent, Gifts, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Ariens, Monroe and Melanie, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Arient, Jim, 1993-1995 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Art Accession Committee, 1979-1982 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Art Department Gallery Committee, 1984-1987 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Art Department Task Force on Long Range Planning, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Art History Department, Letters & Sciences, 1983-1985 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Art History Gallery Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Art Museum Committee, 1975-1980 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Art Museum Policy Committee Minutes, 1983-1984 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Arts Education Media Research Center, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Bader, Dr. Alfred, 1975-1985 (Box 19, Folder 15-16)
    - Balsley, John and Diane, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Barnes, Carl, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Basquin, Kit, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Baum, Chancellor Werner, 1971-1975 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Beloit College, 1986-1987 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Berman, Fred (Robert Miller), 1985 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Bishop, Gary, 1984-1985 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Bookstore Calendar, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Breitz, Candice, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Brotherus, Elina, 2002-2003 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Brunhart Gift, 1993-1994 (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Buchanan, Roderick, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Building Commission, E.J. Dennis, 1986-1987 (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - Butter, Roy, 1993-1994 (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - Calendar of Exhibitions, 1990-1996 (Box 19, Folder 31-32)
    - Cho, Kyoung Ae, 2000-2002 (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - Clippings, 1970-1988 (Box 19, Folder 34-37)
    - College for Kids, 1991-1993 (Box 19, Folder 38-40)
    - College for Kids Invitation, undated (Box 19, Folder 41)
    - Committee on Institutional Cooperation, 1974-1976 (Box 19, Folder 42)
    - Cron, Florence S., Gift, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 43)
    - Currie, Jamal, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 44)
    - Designing Educators, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 45)
    - Durant, Sam, 2001-2002 (Box 19, Folder 46)
    - Elvehjem Museum of Art, University of Wisconsin Madison, 1983-1986 (Box 19, Folder 47)
    - Equipment, UWM Art Museum, 1981-1983 (Box 19, Folder 48)
    - Exhibition Committee
      - 1973-1974 (Box 19, Folder 49)
      - Annual Reports, 1965-1967 (Box 19, Folder 50)
    - Exhibition Schedules, 1991-1993 (Box 19, Folder 51)
    - Exhibitions, 1984-1986 (Box 19, Folder 52)
    - Faculty Meeting Minutes and Announcements, 1975-1976 (Box 19, Folder 53)
    - Feitler, Robert, Gift, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 54)
    - Fiber R/Evolution
      - Administrative
        - General, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 1)
        - Artists/Objects List, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 2)
        - Clippings, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 3)
        - Correspondence
          - Mary Jane Jacob, 1984-1986 (Box 20, Folder 4)
          - Mildred Constantine, 1984-1986 (Box 20, Folder 5)
          - Milwaukee Art Museum/UWM, 1984-1986 (Box 20, Folder 6)
          - Neda Al-Hilali, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 7)
        - Fibers, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 8)
        - Juried Selection, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 9)
        - Letters and Forms to the Artists Juried Section, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 10)
        - Photography/Slides, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 11)
        - Press Relations Information, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 12)
        - Touring Information, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 13)
        - Wall Label, undated (Box 20, Folder 14)
      - Rejected, Juried Section
        - Bennett, Sherry, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 15)
        - Bentovim, Yael, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 16)
        - Campbell, Patricia, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 17)
        - Feldman, Bella Tabak (Withdrawn), 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 18)
        - Fey, Gary, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 19)
        - Gothard, Lark, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 20)
        - Gunderson, Marla, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 21)
        - Jacobs, Virginia, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 22)
        - Mooney, David R., 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 23)
        - Rothstein, Scott, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 24)
        - Sadia, G. Jesse Jr., 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 25)
      - Accepted, Juried Section
        - Akamine, Estelle M., 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 26)
        - Andrews, Dana Romalo, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 27)
        - Bergner, Lanny, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 28)
        - Bero, Mary, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 29)
        - Campbell, Katherine, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 30)
        - Doherty, Allison, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 31)
        - Ekhardt, Barbara, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 32)
        - Elliott, Lillian and Pat Hickman, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 33)
        - Felix, Deborah J., 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 34)
        - Ferguson, Tamiko Kawata, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 35)
        - Fletcher, Mollie, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 36)
        - Fox, Shelia, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 37)
        - Garrett, John G., 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 38)
        - Hall, Lynn G., 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 39)
        - Hammer, Joanne, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 40)
        - Healy, Sherry, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 41)
        - Hiebel, Kaye, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 42)
        - Iwata, Kiyomi, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 43)
        - Jones, Geary A. and David Johnson, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 44)
        - Knowles, Elizabeth B., 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 45)
        - Lackey, Jane, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 46)
        - Lechman, Patti, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 47)
        - Lippold, Larry J., 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 48)
        - Lyman, Susan, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 49)
        - Markarian, Janet, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 50)
        - Michaels-Paque, Joan, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 51)
        - Minkowitz, Norma, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 52)
        - Nelson, Susan Venable, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 53)
        - Nicholson, Laura Foster, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 54)
        - Pollack, Junco Sato, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 55)
        - Quinton, Sara, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 56)
        - Romanoke, Jill, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 57)
        - Sheehan, Diane, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 58)
        - Sisson, Karyl, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 59)
        - Stahlecker, Karen, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 60)
        - Strommen, Kim, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 61)
        - Tate, Blair, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 62)
        - Tuttle, Elizabeth, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 63)
        - Utterback, Connie, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 64)
        - Ward, Evelyn Svec, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 65)
        - Wilson, Anne, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 66)
    - Fine Arts Gallery Committee, 1975-1979 (Box 21, Folder 1-2)
    - Fine Arts Scheduling Committee, 1996-1997 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Fishman, Marvin and Janet, 1977-1994 (Box 21, Folder 4-6)
    - Fitch Theft, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 1)
      Restricted
    - Franklin, Dr. Richard, 1993-1995 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Freeman, Michael, Gift, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Friebert, Joseph, 1992-1993 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Friend, Kathy, 1987-1988 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Funk, Verne, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Galavaris, George, 1975-1977 (Box 21, Folder 12-13)